<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Noss</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Noss</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Keebio Iris Rev 8 Review</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/reviews/keebio-iris-rev-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/reviews/keebio-iris-rev-8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;backstory&#34; class=&#34;relative group&#34;&gt;Backstory &lt;span class=&#34;absolute top-0 w-6 transition-opacity opacity-0 -start-6 not-prose group-hover:opacity-100&#34;&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;group-hover:text-primary-300 dark:group-hover:text-neutral-700&#34; style=&#34;text-decoration-line: none !important;&#34; href=&#34;#backstory&#34; aria-label=&#34;Anchor&#34;&gt;#&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since I was 16, I have had back issues. When I was 19, I was officially diagnosed with scholiosis. This causes pain all over my body but can usually start from my lower back or my shoulders/neck area. I actively make changes in my lifestyle in an attempt to avoid the pain that I endur everyday. Two years ago, I was working and couldn&amp;rsquo;t hold my mouse or type on my keyboard without pain shooting through my arms. I was 20 and about a year and a half into my IT career and I thought it was about to come to an end. A year and a half later, I found out about split keyboards after watching The Primeagen talk about using a split keyboard. I thought they were ugly and dumb. Fast forward a few months and that pain is back again but this time it was more frequent. I told myself I can push through it, wondering if this is something I could endur my whole life. Recently I saw Primeagen &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UrxkO4DM67M&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noreferrer&#34;&gt;talk about the glove 80&lt;/a&gt;. I gave it some serious thought but then I decided not to. Then I saw a lot of other videos about split keyboards. They were primarily mentioning how they reduce strain in the neck/shoulders area. This was an area that causes pain but I had never tried to stop the pain there before. I did no research to see if that is true, I just decided to jump in. The pre-built ones were out of my price range&amp;hellip; until I found the Keebio Iris Rev 8. I could afford it and I wanted it to be a gateway into my new split keyboard addiction.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
